Guide to the First Congregational Church of Portland records 1849-2016
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Groups, 1863-2015; Series B
  - Christian Endeavor, Subseries 7
    - Newsletters - issues of The Monthly Aggress, 1914 February-April (Box-folder 31/14)
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor - Correspondence and records re Pilgrim Chapel, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 31/15)
    - Reports, 1914-1923; undated (Box-folder 31/16)
    - Roll book, 1909-1914 (Box-folder 31/17)
    - Rosters, 1914 (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Chrysalis Club records, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 31/19)
  - Church Council, Subseries 8
    Known until 1994 as the Executive Council.
    - Information re Ad Hoc Birthday Gift Committee, 1991 December 16 (Box-folder 31/20)
    - Church profile discussion, 2009 July 15 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1965; 1978; 1980 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1991-1993; 1996 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - "A Look Ahead", 1951 November 27 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1920 September - 1922 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Meeting minutes, 1940 November 6 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Meeting minutes, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1963 September-1964 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Meeting minutes, 1965 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Meeting minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1968 April-December (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1969 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1970 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1971 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Meeting minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 32/20)
    - Meeting minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Meeting minutes, 1977 September - 1979 April (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Meeting minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Meeting minutes, 1981 (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Meeting minutes and notices, 1982 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1986 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1987 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Meeting minutes and reports, 1989 (Box-folder 33/8)
      Includes some attached documents.
    - Meeting minutes, 1990 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1991 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 1992 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Meeting minutes, 1993 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Meeting minutes, 1994 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - Meeting minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - Meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 33/15)
    - Meeting minutes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 33/16)
    - Meeting minutes and notices, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 33/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 33/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 2005 (Box-folder 33/19)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2006 (Box-folder 33/20)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2007 (Box-folder 33/21)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2008 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2009 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Special meeting minutes and attached documents, 2009 September 2 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2010 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2011 (Box-folder 34/5)
      Includes some attached documents and reports.
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2012 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2013 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2014 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Outreach program records, 1964 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Proposals, recommendations, and resolutions, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Recommendation to the church, circa 1950 November (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Recommendations made to council, circa 1966 February (Box-folder 34/12)
    - Report, 1921 June 23 (Box-folder 34/13)
    - Reports, 1988 (Box-folder 34/14)
    - Associate pastor's report, 1965 August 2 (Box-folder 34/15)
    - Report re pillar replacement, 1994 September 14 (Box-folder 34/16)
    - Retreat, 1982 (Box-folder 34/17)
    - Roster of Executive Council, Division of Social Action, 1973 (Box-folder 34/18)
    - Roster, 1955 (Box-folder 34/19)
    - Rosters, 1966-1971; 1973; 1978 (Box-folder 34/20)
    - Rosters, 1983-1991; 1994 (Box-folder 34/21)
    - Meeting sign-in sheets, 2014 (Box-folder 34/22)
    - Meeting sign-in sheets, 2015 (Box-folder 34/23)
    - Statement to Executive Council by Lester van Fleet, 1965 September 22 (Box-folder 34/24)
    - Transition Team discussion, 2009 June 17 (Box-folder 34/25)
  - Church Growth Team records, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 34/26)
  - Church Hymnal Committee reports, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 34/27)
  - Department of Church/Religious Work reports, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 34/28)
  - Coffee House Steering Committee records, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 34/29)
  - Congregational Church Building Society records, 1893, 1902 (Box-folder 34/30)
  - Board of Deaconesses reports, circa 1917-1925; 1947 (Box-folder 34/31)
  - Board of Deacons annual reports, circa 1917-1926; 1936-1937; 1947 (Box-folder 34/32)
  - Dual Services Committee report and accompanying letter, 1960 August (Box-folder 34/33)
  - Records and correspondence re Edward Albrecht Memorial Committee of 100, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 34/34)
  - Finance Committee/Commission meeting minutes and reports, 2006; 2010; 2012-2014 (Box-folder 34/35)
  - Forum Committee., Subseries 9
    Also called Sunday Forum Committee.
    See also Series K: Lectures.
    - Organizational meeting minutes, 1984 May-July (Box-folder 34/36)
    - Meeting minutes and attached documents, 1984 August 14 (Box-folder 34/37)
    - Meeting minutes, 1984 September - 1985 May (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Meeting minutes and attached documents, 1985 June - 1986 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Notice for organizational meeting, 1984 May (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Roster, 1986 (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Annual reports of the Guild for 1917 and 1918, circa 1918-1919 (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Correspondence re research on Helping Hand Mission Band, 1954 (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Helping Hand Mission Band treasurer's book, 1896-1897 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Inclusive Language Task Force records, 1994 (Box-folder 35/8)
  - Committee on Inter Church and Community Relations report, circa 1972 (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Joint/combined group records, Subseries 10
    Inseparable documents and volumes relating to multiple groups.
    - Committee and officer reports, 2011 January-August (Box-folder 35/10)
    - Invitation for meeting with Deacons and Deaconesses, 1923 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Minutes book of Executive Council and Spiritual Life Committee, 1931 January 22 - 1940 February (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Minutes for Music Committee and Spiritual Life Commission joint meetings, 1966; 1992 October - 1993 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Music, Art, Drama (MAD) and Artreach scrapbook, 1980-1987 (Box-folder Box 133)
      Includes some photographs.
  - Ladies Aid Society, Subseries 11
    - Research files (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Program for annual bazaar, 1895 December 4 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Cookbook, "Dainty Dishes", 1903 (Box-folder 35/16)
    - Correspondence and invitations, 1886-1915 (Box-folder 35/17)
    - Finances - Account book, 1863-1876; 1884 (Box-folder 35/18)
    - Financial notes, circa 1883-1908 (Box-folder 35/19)
    - Finances - Dues paid, 1884 September - 1893 April (Box-folder 35/20)
    - Finances - Dues paid, 1895 September - 1902 March (Box-folder 35/21)
    - Financial records, 1905, circa 1908 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Finances - Account ledger, 1912 January 1 - 1919 February 5 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Financial records, 1915 June (Box-folder 36/3, 112/7)
    - Financial report, 1907 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - "Gatherings by the Wayside", 1895 (Box-folder 36/5)
      Book of quotes and poems published by the Ladies Aid Society.
    - Historical synopsis of the Ladies Aid Society, undated (Box-folder 36/6)
    - History of Ladies Aid Societies, circa 1900 (Box-folder 36/7)
      Notecards with handwritten text about the different iterations of the Ladies Aid Society.
    - "History of the Ladies' Aid Society, 1883-1908" by Edna Himes Reid (Box-folder 36/8)
      Typescript.
    - History of the Ladies Aid Society, 1908 (Box-folder 36/9)
      Pen version.
    - History of the Ladies Aid Society, 1908 (Box-folder 36/10)
      Pencil draft version
    - List of visiting congregants, circa 1900 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Minutes book, 1862 June 10 - 1877 June 7 (Box-folder 36/12)
      Also includes constitution of the Ladies Aid Society.
    - Minutes book, 1883 June 17 - 1891 July 1 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Minutes book, 1891 September 9 - 1898 September 13 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - Minutes book, 1898 December - 1904 September (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Minutes book, circa 1920 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Passbook, 1902 April - 1908 September (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Report for 1898, circa 1899 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Reports, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 November 24 (Box-folder 37/5)
      Booklet written by Elizabeth Eggert.
    - Correspondence re "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1924 (Box-folder 37/6)
      Primarily thank-you letters sent to Elizabeth Eggert.
    - Typescripts of "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Complete draft of "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - First segment of draft for "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Second segment of draft for "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 (Box-folder 37/10)
    - Third segment of draft for "Review of the Work and Activities of the Ladies' Aid Organizations of the First Congregational Church", 1923 (Box-folder 37/11)
    - Roll book, 1893 September - 1904 September (Box-folder 37/12)
    - Roll book, 1905 September - 1912 August (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Life Club records, circa 1932-1933 (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Literary Circle readings and debate topics, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 37/15)
    Includes the text of the lecture "The Domestic and Social Life of the Early Colonists" and the debate "Does the History of Political Parties in America Prove That a Political Career Is Debasing to Manhood?"
  - Marketing and Community Relations director's reports, 2014 (Box-folder 37/16)
  - Membership Commission, Subseries 12
    Also called the New Membership Committee and the Membership Outreach Commission.
    - Promotional brochures and registration forms, circa 1940-1975 (Box-folder 37/17)
    - Events and greeters calendars, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 37/18)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1966-1967; 1973-1978 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Correspondence, memos, guidelines, and surveys, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Flyer for new members picnic, circa 2001 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - List of young couples invited to Reverend Royald V. Caldwell's residence on June 13, 1967 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Meeting minutes, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Meeting minutes, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Meeting minutes and reports, 2008 October 14; 2010-2014 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - "Membership Information", 1963 February 22 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - Report, 1926 January 14 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - Rosters, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - Rosters, 1971-1972; 1978 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - Rosters, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - Welcome Team manual, 1997 (Box-folder 38/18)
  - Men's groups, Subseries 13
    Includes materials relating several groups which overlapped and/or were closely related.
    - First Church Men - Event programs, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - First Church Men newsletters, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 38/20)
    - First Church Men membership roster, circa 1931 (Box-folder 38/21)
    - First Church Men - Song lyrics, circa 1931 (Box-folder 38/22)
    - Typescript of article about Laymen's Fellowship, 1930 (Box-folder 38/23)
    - Laymen's Fellowship - Correspondence, 1953 November (Box-folder 38/24)
    - Laymen's Fellowship - Institute of Churchmanship program, 1955 March 13 (Box-folder 38/25)
    - Men's Brotherhood/First Church Men - Father-and-Son Supper invitation and RSVP cards, 1929, circa 1932 (Box-folder 38/26)
    - Clipping re Men's Brotherhood, 1928 April 9 (Box-folder 38/27)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 38/28)
    - Church Brotherhood - Ephemera, 1927 - circa 1932 (Box-folder 38/29)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Treasurer's report, 1924 February 11 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Meeting minutes, notices, etc., 1927-1928 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Menu for Ladies' Night Banquet, 1914 June 1 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Menu for unidentified event, circa 1928 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Annual reports, 1918-1924 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Men's Brotherhood - Roster of officers, circa 1928 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Minute Men recruitment cards, undated (Box-folder 39/7)
    - Men's Sunday Service League calendars, 1902 November-December (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Program for Division of Missions events, 1953 (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Division of Missions - Program for international dinner, 1955 October 26 (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Missionary Department reports, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Report of Department of Missions for 1942, circa 1943 (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Music-Art-Drama (MAD) Committee, Subseries 14
    Also briefly known as Music-Art-Drama-Dance (MADD) Committee.
    See also Series M: Performing and visual arts.
    - By-law amendments re Music-Art-Drama-Dance Committee, 1982 January 31 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1972, 1983 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Meeting minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - Meeting minutes, 1975-1981 March (Box-folder 39/16)
    - Meeting minutes, 1981 April-1984 May (Box-folder 39/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 1984 September - 1985 July (Box-folder 39/18)
    - Park Block Revels Steering Committee meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 39/19)
    - Recommended policy regarding musical events, 1973 October 25 (Box-folder 39/20)
    - Presentation proposing an Arts Coordinator, 1984 November 7 (Box-folder 39/21)
    - Report, 1976 (Box-folder 39/22)
    - Rosters, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 39/23)
    - Scrapbook/album, 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 134)
  - Music Committee, Subseries 15
    See also Series L: Music.
    - Research files (Box-folder 39/24)
    - Letter re Music Department by-laws, 1920 December 30 (Box-folder 39/25)
    - By-laws, 1974 (Box-folder 39/26)
    - Correspondence - letter from Music Committee chairman to Board of Trustees, 1904 August 17 (Box-folder 39/27)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 39/28)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 39/29)
    - Finances - Budget, 1952 (Box-folder 39/30)
    - Financial records, 1966-1982 (Box-folder 39/31)
    - Meeting minutes, 1935 June 2 (Box-folder 39/32)
    - Meeting minutes, 1969 October - 1971 (Box-folder 39/33)
    - Meeting minutes, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 39/34)
    - Meeting minutes, 1977 December - 1979 (Box-folder 39/35)
    - Meeting minutes, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 39/36)
    - Meeting minutes, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 39/37)
    - Meeting minutes, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 39/38)
    - Meeting minutes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 39/39)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1990-1993; 1999 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Summer newsletter, 1960 August 25 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Reports, 1920-1926 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Report, 1930 September 4 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Annual reports for 1981 and 1985, 1982, 1986 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Organist and Associate Director's report for 1986, 1987 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Rosters, 1969-1990 (Box-folder 40/8)
  - Nesika Group, Subseries 16
    - Financial ledger, 1932-1945 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 1943 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - Records, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 40/12)
      Primarily meeting minutes for 1944-1945.
    - Membership list and Telephone Committee roster, 1941 (Box-folder 40/13)
  - (Box-folder 40/14)
  - (Box-folder 40/15)
  - Oliver Lecture Committee, Subseries 17
    - Helen Oliver Memorial Lectures agreement and related documents, 1977 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - Correspondence and documents re Helen Oliver Memorial Lecture Fund, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 1978; 1990 December - 1992 (Box-folder 40/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 40/19)
    - Meeting minutes, 1997-2000; 2005 (Box-folder 40/20)
    - Report, 2012 January (Box-folder 40/21)
  - (Box-folder 40/22)
  - (Box-folder 40/23)
  - (Box-folder 40/24)
  - Outreach Commission, Subseries 18
    - Letters re designated offerings, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 40/25)
    - Meeting minutes, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 40/26)
    - Meeting minutes, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 40/27)
    - Memo, 1995 April 5 (Box-folder 40/28)
    - Memos re house volunteer schedules, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 40/29)
    - "Reach Out!" newsletters, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 40/30)
    - Documents re sponsoring Kosovar refugees, 1999 (Box-folder 40/31)
    - Reports, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 40/32)
    - Roster, circa 1995 (Box-folder 40/33)
  - Pastoral Relations Commission report, 2011 December (Box-folder 40/34)
  - Ad-Hoc Personnel Committee report, 1983 (Box-folder 40/35)
  - Personnel Committee reports and proposals, 2011 November - 2013 (Box-folder 40/36)
  - Pilgrim Fellowship, Subseries 19
    Also known as Pilgrim Hi Fellowship.
    - Clipping re Pilgrim Fellowship, circa 1962 (Box-folder 40/37)
    - Constitution, circa 1950 (Box-folder 40/38)
    - Correspondence - Letter from Jane Russell Waterfield, WAIF-I.S.S., 1962 May 25 (Box-folder 40/39)
    - Correspondence - Letter to parents re schedule, 1953 (Box-folder 40/40)
    - Materials re death of David Starr at Spirit Lake, Washington, 1956 (Box-folder 40/41)
    - Event programs, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Event programs, flyers, and ephemera, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Flyer for Senior High event, 1985 November (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Junior Diaconate bylaws, circa 1950 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Newsletters - "Grapevine", 1956-1957 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Newsletters - "Raisin Creeper", 1953-1957; 1963 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Newsletters - "The Steeple", 1954 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Pilgrim Fellowship Youth Conference, 1957 February (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Procedures for installation of officers, circa 1950 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Report to Spiritual Life Commission, 1964 May 19 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Reunion programs, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Rosters, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - Scrapbook, 1953-1956 (Box-folder Box 135)
    - Scrapbook, 1957-1959 (Box-folder Box 136)
    - Scrapbook, 1960-1964 (Box-folder Box 137)
    - Collection of sermonettes written 1958-1963 (Box-folder 41/13)
      Published in memory of John ("Butch") Reese.
    - Service programs, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - Service and officer installation programs, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - United Christian Youth constitution, circa 1954 (Box-folder 41/16)
  - Ad-Hoc Program Evaluation and Proposal Committee records, 1988 (Box-folder 41/17)
  - Prudential Committee meeting minutes book, 1898 January 18 - 1903 December 17 (Box-folder 41/18)
  - Prudential Committee meeting minutes book, 1904-1910 (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Prudential Committee meeting minutes, 1910 May 17 - 1918 December 17 (Box-folder 41/20)
  - Ritual Study Group meeting minutes, 2001 January 14 (Box-folder 41/21)
  - History of Rockwood Bible Club, 1905-1955; undated (Box-folder 42/1)
    Bound volume. Includes some photographs.
  - Loose papers accompanying history of Rockwood Bible Club, 1937-1949; undated (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Brief history of Rockwood Bible Club, 1966 (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Rockwood Bible Club - Outline studies, Jeremiah and Ezekiel, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Scrooby Club, Subseries 20
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1959, undated (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Correspondence, 1948; 1952; 1957-1958 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Directories, 1955; 1960; 1966 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Event programs and flyers, 1945-1963 (Box-folder 42/8)
      See also Series M: Performing and vidual arts for materials relating to plays put on by the Scrooby Club.
    - Financial balances and treasurer's reports, 1947-1956; 1962 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Invitations to speaking events, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Meeting minutes, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Meeting minutes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Meeting minutes, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 42/14)
      Includes attached reports and financial balance sheets.
    - Meeting minutes, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - New Year's Eve party invitations, circa 1953-1957 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Newsletters - "Scrooby Crier", 1940 (Box-folder 42/17)
      Includes some attached notes.
    - Newsletters - "Scrooby Crier", 1946-1949 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Newsletters - "Scrooby Crier", 1950-1954 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Newsletters - "Scrooby Crier", 1955-1959 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Newsletters - "Scrooby Crier", 1960-1964 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Position descriptions, undated (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Annual report for 1946, circa 1947 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Annual report for 1956, 1957 January 4 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Reunion invitation, 1987 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Roster, 1946 October 29 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Senior Adults, Subseries 21
    - Clippings re Senior Adults, 1966 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Correspondence - Letter to Kate Hedin, 1968 April 17 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Event programs and invitations, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Mailing list and meeting attendees, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 43/19)
    - List of programs, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - Rosters, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - Materials re United States Senate Subcommittee on Involuntary Relocation of the Elderly, 1962 December (Box-folder 43/23)
  - Silver Circle, Subseries 22
    A subgroup of the Women's Fellowship.
    - Finances - Treasurer's report for 1918, circa 1919 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Financial records, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Finances - Treasurer's book, 1929-1936 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - History of Silver Circle, 1937 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Transcript of minutes from first meeting of Silver Circle, undated (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Minutes book, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Minutes book, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Minutes book, 1930-1940 (Box-folder 44/7)